tripmama.com 2009-08-06

# TripMama Privacy Policy

|   
---  
| Introduction  
---  
[ ](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.tripmama.com&sealid=101) **TripMama.com is strongly committed to protecting your privacy.** **TripMama** is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site [http://www.tripmama.com](http://www.tripmama.com/). Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. We collect your name and email address when you sign up to receive our newsletters or when you register to use our forums. If you have trouble accessing the forums, we will use this information to contact you. We do not sell, trade, share or rent your personal information to others. We keep your personal information private and secure. We do not use agents or service providers on our site.  
top  
|   
---  
| Access to Personally Identifiable Information  
---  
If your personally identifiable information changes or if you no longer desire to use our website, you may correct, update, deactivate or delete the account by making the change on the Edit Profile page. You can also email our Customer Support at [feedback@tripmama.com](mailto:feedback@tripmama.com) or call us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information below. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit in the online blogs and forums can be read, collected or used by other users of these forums and blogs and can be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you chose to submit in these forums. To keep you informed about our latest services, we may notify you via email newsletter of any changes or new additions to our site. You may unsubscribe from our email newsletter by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email you receive from us. Other sites accessible through our web site have their own privacy policies and data collection practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. TripMama.com is not responsible for the actions of third parties.  
top  
|   
---  
| Cookies  
---  
This web site uses cookies to personalize your experience at this site, and optionally to speed up the member sign in process. Cookies are information stored on your computer. Cookies are not used to track your movement or perform any function other than to enhance your use of this site. If your browser does not support cookies, or you have not enabled cookies on your browser, many of these time-saving features will not work properly. Also, you need to have cookies enabled in your browser if you want to enter the member’s area. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site Some of our business partners (Traffic Analyzing Software ) use cookies on our site which do not collect any personally identifiable information. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [http://www.tripmama.com](http://www.tripmama.com/) only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  
top  
|   
---  
| Security  
---  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [feedback@tripmama.com](mailto:feedback@tripmama.com)  
top  
|   
---  
| Government and Legal  
---  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.  
top  
|   
---  
| Changes to the Privacy Policy  
---  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement page, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on our homepage.  
top  
|   
---  
| Choice/Opt-out  
---  
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletteor by contacting us at the address below. You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.  
top  
|   
---  
|   
---  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should first contact  
**Customer Service**  
  
One Penn Plaza  
P.O. Box 6246  
New York, NY 10001  
[feedback@tripmama.com](mailto:feedback@tripmama.com).

If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at [ http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.  
  
Privacy Policy last updated on 13 August 2007
